Sandy Co

Cellphone No.: (778) 681-3641

E-mail: sandyyklc@gmail.com

Website: sandyklc.github.io

Profile

Imaginative, empathetic and adaptable UI/UX designer with a goal to tie in user experience and aesthetically pleasing design. Enthusiastic about the processes of user experience research and data-driven design. Boasting great attention to detail, solid understanding of design principles, strong team-oriented work ethic, a love for technology and a creative approach to problem solving.

Education

University of British Columbia

Sep 2016 - May 2020 (Expected) Vancouver, BC, Canada Bachelor of Arts Major in Cognitive Systems: Brain and Cognition Stream, Minor in Commerce

Experience

Undergraduate Teaching Assistant UBC (PHIL220: Symbolic Logic)

Work

Jan 2019 - April 2019 Vancouver, BC, Canada

- Assists the professor in supervising 150 students during exams
- Marks homeworks and exam papers weekly
- Maintains continuous communication with the professor through e-mail and in-person meetings

Graphic Designer DreamBlock (Contract)

May 2018 - Present Vancouver, BC, Canada

 Created graphic materials including whitepapers, presentations and design templates, using primarily Adobe InDesign, Adobe Illustrator and Adobe Photoshop

Digital Marketing Assistant UBC Athletics and Recreation

January 2018 - Sep 2018 Vancouver, BC, Canada

- Assisted with the creation of graphic materials including social media graphics, large format printing, digital signage, using primarily Adobe InDesign
- Maintained, updated and created strategies to improve the functionality and design of the UBC Recreation website using UBC CMS and Wordpress
- Analyzed, and provided feedback and solutions to improve current website's usability and user interface

Experience

President UBC Kababayan: Filipino Students Association

Leadership

May 2018 - April 2019 Vancouver, BC, Canada

- Lead the club's executive team for SY 2018-2019 in planning various events for the year
- Created a strong and welcoming Filipino community in UBC and increased member rate by 20%

Design Tools

 Maintained proper external relations with other clubs and organizations and internal relations with the members of the club

VP-Marketing UBC Kababayan: Filipino Students Association

May 2016 - April 2018 Vancouver, BC, Canada

• Managed social media content and maintained the club's brand image and theme

Skills

Programming Languages

JavaC++SQLPhotoshopInDesignSketchHTML + CSSAssemblyIllustratorAdobe XDInVision

C Javascript

Applied Skills Other Tools

Critiquing Project-Management Microsoft Office Mailchimp
Team Work Ethic Task/Event Planning Wordpress Trello
Campaign + Branding Statistical Analysis Arduino Slack

Spoken Languages

Native/Bilingual Proficiency: English, Filipino Limited Proficiency: Mandarin, Spanish